Big meets bigger.
Rampage is a action, adventure, science fiction film directed by Brad Peyton.
Primatologist Davis Okoye shares an unshakable bond with George, the extraordinarily
intelligent, silverback gorilla who has been in his care since birth.
But a rogue genetic experiment gone awry mutates this gentle
ape into a raging creature of enormous size.
To make matters worse, it’s soon discovered there
are other similarly altered animals.
As these newly created alpha predators tear across North America, destroying everything in their path, Okoye teams with a discredited genetic engineer to secure an
antidote, fighting his way through an ever-changing battlefield, not only to halt a global catastrophe but to save the fearsome creature that was once his friend.
Davis Okoye, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Dr. Kate Caldwell, played by Naomie Harris.
Claire Wyden, played by Malin Åkerman.
Harvey Russell, played by Jeffrey Dean Morgan.
Brett Wyden, played by Jake Lacy.
Burke, played by Joe Manganiello.
Rampage is a 2018 American science fiction monster film loosely based on the
video game series by Midway Games, and starring Dwayne Johnson.
The film was directed by Brad Peyton and written by
Ryan Engle, Carlton Cuse, Ryan J.
Condal, and Adam Sztykiel.
Naomie Harris, Malin Akerman, Jake Lacy, and Jeffrey
Dean Morgan star in supporting roles.
In the film, a primatologist and his leucistic gorilla friend, George, team-up to stop a pair of other animals that, along with
George, have been mutated into raging beasts with fluctuating enhancements thanks to a gene-manipulating pathogen.
The film is the third collaboration between Peyton and Johnson, following
Journey 2: The Mysterious Island (2012) and San Andreas (2015).
Principal photography began in April 2017 in Chicago.
The film was released in the United States on April 13, 2018, by Warner Bros.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $428
million on a $120–140 million budget.
The film explores themes of monster, wolf, mutation, gorilla, giant monster.
The tone is thought_provoking.